[
    {
        "QUESTION": "Frankly my dear, I don't give a___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "damn",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "care",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "worry",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "dam"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "I'm going to give him an offer he can't___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "refuse",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "accept",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "knock back",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "decline"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "Toto, I've got a feeling we are not in____ anymore",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "kansas",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "new york",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "texas",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "Boston"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "Go ahead, make my___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "day",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "night",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "afternoon",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "morning"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "May the___be with you",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "force",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "power",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "source",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "energy"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "Fasten your seat belts. It's going to be a bumpyâ€¦",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "night",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "ride",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "slide",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "evening"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "What we've got here is failure to___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "communicate",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "talk",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "speak up",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "connect"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "Love means never having to say your___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "sorry",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "happy",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "sad",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "guilty"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "The stuff that___are made of",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dreams",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "goals",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "aspirations",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "fantasies"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I have a___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dream",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "goal",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "thought",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "challenge"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I think this is the beginning of a beautiful___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "friendship",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "relationship",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "acquaintance",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "alliance"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Made it, Ma! Top of the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "world",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "mountain",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "building",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "tree"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Bond.___Bond",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "james",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "john",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "jeff",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "jason"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " There's no place like___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "home",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "work",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "house",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "homeland"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Round up the usual___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "suspects",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "team",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "people",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "questionableople"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " You're going to need a bigger___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "boat",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "car",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "bike",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "house"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___be back",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "i'll",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "you'll",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "they'll",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "It'll"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Life is like a___of chocolates",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "box",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "carton",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "packet",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "stash"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I see___people",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dead",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "many",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "several",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "ghost"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Houston, we have a___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "problem",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "situation",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "issue",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "concern"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " There's no crying in___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "baseball",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "basketball",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "football",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "tennis"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___is good",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "greed",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "love",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "power",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "success"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "Keep your friends close, but your___closer",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "enemies",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "family",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "teammates",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "partner"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " A boy's best friend is his___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "mother",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "father",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "brother",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "sister"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Get your stinking paws off me, you damned dirty___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "ape",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "dog",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "monkey",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "rat"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I feel the need, the need for___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "speed",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "power",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "success",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "money"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I'm___of the world",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "king",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "queen",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "prince",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "on top"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Show me the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "money",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "power",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "passion",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "greed"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " The good, the bad and the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "ugly",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "beautiful",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "distasteful",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "pretty"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Money makes the world go___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "round",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "faster",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "smoother",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "better"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___out of it",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "snap",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "come",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "break",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "move"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Snap, crackle and___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "pop",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "break",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "jump",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "sling"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Who's on___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "first",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "second",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "third",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "top"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " My___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "precious",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "valuable",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "important",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "expensive"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " How you___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "doin",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "going",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "doing",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "travelling"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Hello___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "gorgeous",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "beautiful",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "pretty",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "bella"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Eat my___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "shorts",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "pants",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "skirt",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "shoes"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Honey___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "i'm home",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "i'm back",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "i'm coming",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "lets go"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Survival of the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fittest",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "strongest",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "smartest",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "richest"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dog",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "cat",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "rat",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "person"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Student becomes the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "master",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "teacher",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "leader",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "boss"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " The only thing we have to___is fear itself",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fear",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "be scared of",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "worry about",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "avoid"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " If you can___it you can do it",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dream",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "see",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "feel",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "touch"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Life is all about taking___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "risks",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "chances",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "opportunities",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "leaps"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Laugh about your___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "mistakes",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "errors",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "faults",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "flaws"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Strength lies in differences, not in",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "simmilarities",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "muscle",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "size",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "familiarities"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " if you want to soar in life you must first learn to___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fly",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "leap",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "jump",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "glide"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___demands singleness of purpose",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "success",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "achievement",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "happiness",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "prosperity"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___is the best medicine",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "laughter",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "positivity",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "panadol",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "antibiotics"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___it's two letters too long",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "impossible",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "unbelievable",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "unachievable",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "impracticle"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " If you____in it, then anything is possible",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "believe",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "trust",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "thnk",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "have faith"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Every day should be passed as if it were to be our___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "last",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": " final",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "end",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "finish"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " An___for an___will make the whole world blind",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "eye",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "ear",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "nose",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "mouth"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " If you want something done, ask a___person",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "busy",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "lazy",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "trustworthy",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "honest"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " It is only this who never do anything who never make___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "mistakes",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "errors",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "faults",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "changes"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " There is always room for___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "improvement",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "change",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "adjustments",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "alterations"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Real___is doing something nice for someone who will never find out",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "generosity",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "politeness",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "honesty",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "kindness"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " You can't handle the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "truth",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "facts",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "reality",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "circumstances"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " The best way to make your dreams come true is to___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "wake up",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "stay asleep",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "work hard",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "always dream"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " You can't hold a___down without staying down with him",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "man",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "person",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "female",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "woman"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Slow and steady win the___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "race",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "event",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "fastest",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "pursuit"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Yeah? Well, at least I'm not___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "ugly",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "disgusting",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "daggy",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "shaggy"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " There's an awful lot you can tell about a person by their___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "shoes",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "feet",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "jeans",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "jumper"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " You are the___thing that every happened to me",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "worst",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "best",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "hardest",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "easiest"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " No___but what we make for ourselves",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fate",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "chance",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "luck",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "coincidence"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " With my___brains and your looks we could go places",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "brains",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "looks",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "genes",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "fortune"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Live for nothing or___for something",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "die",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "live",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "wait",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "hold out"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Nothing is worth more than this___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "day",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "night",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "moment",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "second"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " I like the___of the future better than the history of the past",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "dreams",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "hopes",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "aspirations",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "goals"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": "  Better to ask___than lose your way once",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "twice",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "once",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "three times",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "four times"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " A long___may not be good enough, but a good___is long enough",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "life",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "time",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "day",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "night"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Say hello to my little___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "friend",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "mate",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "pal",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "buddy"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Pursuit of___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "happiness",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "dreams",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "freedom",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "success"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " ___is the first day of the rest of your life",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "today",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "tomorrow",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "now",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "next week"
    },
    {
        "QUESTION": " Your never too old to become___",
        "CORRECT_ANSWER": "younger",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_1": "older",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_2": "newer",
        "WRONG_ANSWER_3": "better"
    }
]